JIM: Previously on Gotham...
On the count of three, instead of telling
me who you love, tell me who to kill.
- Kill Lee.
- You chose Lee because you love Vale.
(GRUNTS)
ALICE: If a person comes into
contact with my blood, it changes them.
Listen to me, I would never
do anything to hurt you.
Kristen? No!
You wanted to save Lee. You
knew he would do the opposite.
You love Lee. Which
means we're done.
I have found someone.
I have no choice
- but to confess my feelings to Ed.
- Da.
Is this is about the tests they're
running on Alice Tetch's blood?
LUCIUS: Yes. The rats were
exhibiting manic tendencies. Violent rage.
- I assume they're, uh, working on a cure.
- Yes, but it could take years.
Nobody move!
What is going on?
I'm afraid your evening
has been hijacked.
BULLOCK: Glasses down!
(GRUNTING)
Is that my dear sister I
see? She's in you, isn't she?
- Ms. Kringle?
- No, my name's Isabella.
You remind me of
someone that I used to know.
I met someone. I think
I'm in love! (LAUGHS)
I want to rejoin the GCPD.
Welcome back, Detective.
(LIQUID SLOSHING)
GCPD! Hands in the air!
Back away slowly.
(SIGHS)
- This ain't what it looks like.
- Explain it to me down at the precinct.
For now, you'd be wise
to keep your mouth shut...
Listen, uh, can
we talk about this?
Uh, be reasonable, man.
- (GROANING)
- Look, I didn't kill anybody, okay?
I'm the cleaner. That's it.
- You're just the cleaner.
- Yeah.
Just the guy who chops up the
bodies and dumps them in a vat of acid.
That's it.
What're you doing, man?
(SHUDDERS) Okay?
Just take me in, okay?
Oh, I bet that's what you want.
For me to read you your rights.
Make sure you get a lawyer.
Two, three years from now, I see
you on some corner, free as a bird.
Any other night, yeah.
It would eat at me,
but, yeah, I'd do it.
Not tonight.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
The Toad, he's the one you
want. He gave me the job.
See, something's gotten into me.
When I see a scumbag like you
my blood starts boiling in my veins.
I just wanna punish
you, make you suffer.
Up until now, I've
been able to control it.
But it's getting
stronger inside of me.
Please,
The Toad, I told you. He's
the one. Just arrest me.
Arrest me!
- We're past that. (SCREAMS)
- Please! (SCREAMS)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
- Morning.
- We knew what we were getting into, right?
When we agreed to let my dad
throw us an engagement party?
(LAUGHING) Oh, we knew.
I mean, who are these
people? (CHUCKLES)
He's very proud of you. And he
wants all of Gotham to know that.
Well, he's succeeded, because
he invited most of the city.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
- How are you so okay with this?
- Because I agree with him.
He should be proud. As am I.
How did I get so lucky?
What is it?
James Gordon is
returning to the GCPD.
- When?
- He starts today.
- Um, how long have you known this?
- A few days.
I'm sorry, I should've
told you sooner.
It's fine.
Is it?
I don't know, Lee.
We agreed he wouldn't
be part of our lives,
and now you're gonna be working
with him. That's a part of our lives.
Do you trust me? Because if
you do, then nothing else matters.
Of course I trust you.
And you're right, you're right.
It's all gonna be okay. It's just...
(SIGHS) When I think about
what happened with Tetch
and, and the things
that Gordon said, I...
So, don't think about it.
I'll try.
But if you accidentally shot
him, I'd be okay with that, too.
(CHUCKLES) No promises.
I'll see you tonight.
Yeah.
OFFICER 1: Lock this bum up.
OFFICER 2: Get out! Come on.
MAN: I'm innocent, I tell ya!
OFFICER 3: Cover the alley.
- Look, stop pulling me so much.
- Hey, you're cute.
Hey, hey, hey!
There you are. We got a call,
Warehouse district. You coming?
That's it? No welcome back?
Please. If we had a big to-do every
time you came back to the GCPD,
we'd never catch any
bad guys. Ándale, partner.
Oh, and, uh... I believe,
this belongs to you.
You coming or what?
Yeah. I'm coming.
What must be broken
before it can be used?
- (CHUCKLES) Eggs!
- Correct.
- As always.
- (GASPS)
Mmm, Edward, you spoil me.
You make it easy.
I'm going to miss you.
I'm only gone two days.
Well, actually, your conference
ends at 1:45 on Monday.
With traffic, that puts
you in at 5:30 into Gotham.
If you leave on time today,
which I'm sure that you will.
- Mmm-hmm.
- You'll be gone 44 and one half hours.
Less than two days.
(CHUCKLES)
I will hold onto that thought.
Cream! I forgot your cream.
Mmm, mmm, mmm!
So what does one do at
a librarians' conference?
It would bore you.
Nothing that you would say,
do, or think could bore me.
Oh. In that case, let me
read you my schedule.
- ED: Whoo!
- (CHUCKLES)
(WHISTLES)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Where did those
glasses come from?
These? These are my back-up
pair. I normally wear contacts.
(GASPS) I thought you knew that.
(GULPS)
Is something wrong?
Edward, what is it?
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Excuse me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
It's just a pair of glasses.
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
KRINGLE: I remember
you loved that style on me.
(GASPS)
(GASPS) Oh, dear.
I haven't upset you,
have I, Ed? (GIGGLES)
I would've thought you would've
been used to seeing people in mirrors.
You're just in my head.
Like that makes a difference.
But honestly, besides the
fact that she looks just like me,
you went from someone who
files papers in a police station
to someone who files books in
a library. That's super original.
You and Isabella are...
You're somewhat different.
Well, I'm dead.
(CHUCKLES) And she's alive.
But how long will that last?
- Until you...
- I...
(MIMICS CHOKING)
I would never hurt Isabella.
Bet you would've said
the same thing about me.
Face it, Ed. You're a killer.
It's only matter of time...
(SIGHING)
BULLOCK: Okay, so.
A Uni ID'd the vic.
One Paulie Penopolus,
aka Paulie Pennies.
- Clean up guy for the Gotham underworld.
- Bingo.
I'm thinking it was some kind of business
deal. Maybe an unhappy customer.
Perhaps a competitor?
Good place to start.
Hey, listen, seriously, Jim,
I'm glad you're back.
Me too, Harv. Feels good.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
(OFFICER GAGGING)
This wasn't just business.
We should call Barnes.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Do you know why I'm here?
Oh, yes. Yes, indeed.
She's in there, isn't she?
Inside of you.
Hello, sister dear.
Just tell me,
you grew up with your sister,
you've seen this virus first hand.
How do I beat it?
Hmm, I believe the
way this works is
you give me something. I
give you something. Tick-tock.
- How's about I let you keep your teeth?
- Or?
My sister's virus
is a beautiful thing,
it makes the darkest
parts of a person sing.
What darkness in you
has Alice brought to life?
Tell me that, and I'll tell
you everything I know.
Criminals.
The guilty.
My anger at them.
Oh, but it's not anger I see.
Rage.
Violent, bloody rage.
All right, Tetch, my turn.
Is there a cure?
(SIGHS)
Yes, there is a cure.
What is it?
You give in, and let my
dear sister win. (LAUGHS)
You think I'm playing!
- Have you heard the voices?
- What voices?
The virus, even as it grows
stronger, waxes and wanes.
You may have the
illusion you're winning.
Then you hear the voices,
those dark voices
from deep within you,
whispering, whispering.
And, finally, you'll see
the world as it really is.
Then there will be no
more Captain Barnes.
Only Alice.
My dear Alice.
(GRUNTS)
You don't know me!
You've dirtied your
hands, haven't you?
And now you're desperately
trying to make it right.
I can make it right.
- (KNOCKS ON DOOR)
- (DOOR BUZZES)
You're back.
I'm back.
I suppose it was
only a matter of time.
Once a cop, always a cop.
For better or worse,
this is where I belong.
- How's Vale?
- Good. I think.
Well, she's out of
the hospital anyway.
- You two are not...
- No.
I'm not trying to
make this awkward.
Why would it be?
We're both adults.
There's no reason
we can't work together.
I'm glad you feel that
way. Mario agrees?
- He will. Eventually.
- Right.
Our engagement party is tonight.
I only bring it up because a
few people here are going.
- Now it's awkward, isn't it?
- A little.
You wanna know
about the two bodies
- that, were found this morning?
- Yes.
I've only done the
preliminary examination.
But that John Doe in the acid?
His face had been removed.
Removed? How?
Scalpel? Razor blade? Whoever did
it knew exactly what they were doing.
- I'll have more for you soon.
- Okay.
Jim.
I think you made the right
decision, coming back.
BULLOCK: (DISTORTED) I know this
doesn't exactly look like just business.
But, right now, we're thinking
(CLEARLY) whoever paid Paulie
Pennies to dispose of the body
in the bathtub also might have
killed him to tie up some loose ends.
Uh-huh.
Jim, good to see you with
a shield again. And a tie.
- Captain. Good to be back.
- Bullock was just filling me in.
- Hell of a one to catch on your first day.
- Yeah. (SIGHS)
It's the preliminary
report from Lee.
John Doe had his face removed.
Trying to cover up his identity?
I don't know, maybe. But the
acid would've done that anyway.
I'm running point on this one.
- Honestly, Captain...
- That's cool.
Uh, look, I know
I've been away...
Maybe that's why you've
forgotten how things go around here.
- I give you an order, and you follow it.
- Which, for the record, Captain,
I totally support.
I'm taking point on this. I'm
not giving you the day off.
Follow the physical
evidence, Bullock.
- Report back to me.
- Aye aye.
Jim,
I didn't mean to
bite your head off.
It's just sometimes the
ugliness here gets to me.
No need to explain. Let me
know if you need anything.
And, uh...
Don't let the bastards
haze you too hard, rookie.
(CHUCKLES) Yes, sir.
Gordon.
Here's the one you wanted, Captain.
Uh, mid-level felon. Goes by The Toad.
Yeah, that's him. Thank you.
ED: Maybe she's right.
What if there's something
about Miss Kringle's... Kristen's...
Isabella's face.
What if there's something about
her face that unlocks this side of me?
What if I do hurt her?
- Oswald?
- Yes?
You're smiling.
- I was?
- Yes.
Oh. (STAMMERS)
I was just thinking
how darned lucky Isabella is.
You love her, yet to protect her
you are willing to break up with her.
Beautiful. Sad.
- But beautiful.
- So you think I should break up with her.
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought that's
what we were talking about.
- Oh. Certainly, I would never pressure...
- No, you're right.
If I did hurt her, I would
never forgive myself.
(SCOFFS)
That life would put her in your path
again only to snatch her from you.
- Why?
- I can't do it.
- What?
- I can't break up with her.
- But you said yourself...
- I need you to do it for me.
Would you do that? I
would be forever in your debt.
Just be gentle.
Of course.
I'm looking for a punk who
supposedly frequents this rat hole.
Goes by "The Toad."
MAN: Who's askin'?
Captain Nathaniel
Barnes of the GCPD.
How about you and I
go down to the precinct,
and you can answer
some questions.
Blow, pig.
- (GRUNTING)
- (BONES CRUNCHING)
(GROANING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
I wanna know about
Paulie Pennies.
The body he was getting rid of
last night. Where did it come from?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Maybe you want me to
open that mouth for you?
Okay. Stop. I hired Paulie!
- But I'm just the go-between!
- (GRUNTS)
I'm getting so sick
of hearing that.
No one's responsible for
anything. Everyone's a middleman.
- I want a name!
- Symon. Okay?
And Dr. Symon. He's a
big time plastic surgeon!
So, what?
He likes cutting people's
faces off for kicks? Try again!
No! He's got a side business.
You get in trouble. You need
a new face. He gives you one!
A new face? Whose?
I don't know. I just get
rid of the bodies! That's all!
(GROANING)
Oh, you think you're
not guilty, but you are.
Stop, okay? Stop! It's Symon.
(STUTTERS) He's
the one you want!
You're a cop!
(GASPING)
Symon, huh?
Take me to him.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Mayor Cobblepot?
Hello, Isabella. May I?
Um, of course.
(COBBLEPOT SIGHS)
Going somewhere?
Just for a couple of nights.
But, I was hoping to
talk to Ed before I left.
Um, tried calling
him. Is he okay?
Hmm. Yes.
How shall I put this?
It's over. (CHUCKLES)
Excuse me?
He is not going to see you
anymore. Do not try to contact him.
That door is closed.
Have a nice life.
Oh... (GASPS)
Oh, my. (SNIFFS)
It is a shock.
But, besides your odd
resemblance to his ex,
a certain facility with riddles,
compulsion for order,
what is it that you two
really have in common?
Edward is a person of exceptional
intelligence and imagination.
He deserves to be appreciated
by someone on his own level.
And you, my dear,
are simply not.
Best to end things now.
You're right.
I don't deserve him.
Glad we agree. Bye.
But I'm not gonna let him go.
(SNIFFLES) He loves
me, and I love him.
Do you know how
rare that is, Mr. Mayor?
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Of course, you do.
Because you love him, too.
I can see it.
(SIGHS) I'm not even jealous.
- I don't think that you understand...
- It was my glasses this morning.
They reminded
him of Miss Kringle.
He's afraid he's going to
hurt me like he hurt her.
Listen to me, you little idiot,
I am telling you one last time.
Let Ed go.
No.
I will write to him. I will
make him understand
he has nothing to fear.
I'm not gonna let him go.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CHUCKLES) Very well.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
(SIGHS)
- You better not have been lying to me.
- I'm not.
This is his place. You're
not going to kill me, are you?
I'm trying.
- I'm about to take the face.
- (MUFFLED WHIMPERING)
Be here in an hour, and
we can do the transplant.
You haven't eaten
today, have you?
Very good.
I have to thank you, my dear,
for taking such care of your skin.
Excellent elasticity.
Now, hold still.
(MUFFLED PROTESTING)
(DOOR SLAMS OPEN)
- Who's there? Quiet!
- (MUFFLED SHOUTING)
Or we will forgo any anesthesia.
- I said, who's there?
- GCPD.
You're under arrest. Go for it.
Please.
(WHIMPERING)
- I surrender.
- Ma'am, you all right?
(SNARLS SOFTLY)
How many?
- Excuse me?
- How many have you killed?
How many faces have you taken?
I have the right to an attorney.
I wish to invoke
that right, now.
VOICES: (WHISPERING)
Guilty! Guilty! Guilty!
- Who's there?
- No one. It's only me.
VOICES: He's guilty.
Guilty. Guilty. Guilty. Guilty.
What is wrong with you?
(GRUNTING)
- (PANTS) What are you doing? Arrest me!
- (GUN COCKING)
VOICES: Guilty! Guilty!
I'm not resisting!
Guilty!
He's guilty!
Guilty.
LUCIUS: The point Dr. Thompkins
hopes you pay particular attention to
is the level of strength required to
sever Paulie Pennies' head from his torso.
And what level
would that be, Lucius?
Extreme.
Extreme strength, got it.
As for the other victim in the bathtub
we haven't gotten any hits on his prints.
But a puncture mark
in his arm suggests
he was drugged prior to
having his face removed.
I'll run toxicology, let you
know what I come up with.
- Thanks, Lucius.
- Yup.
It's good to have
you back, Gordon.
Lucius, you're in
forensics, not the ME.
Is there a reason Lee
didn't bring this herself?
Dr. Thompkins is already gone
for the day. Her engagement party.
Right.
I hear it's gonna
be quite the affair.
Beautiful women.
Free booze. Canapés.
Harvey, you can go if you want.
I'd much rather spend time here
with my old partner. Much more fun.
Besides, I wasn't invited.
(CHUCKLES)
Captain.
Bullock, book this piece of human
garbage for the murder of John Doe.
You got it, Captain. Come on.
Plastic surgeon. Face
man for the underworld.
He had a girl on the table.
If I had been there
five minutes later...
But you weren't.
You did it, Captain.
Yeah, today.
You know that feeling, Jim,
when you've won the battle
but you know you're
gonna lose the war?
Wars are fought one
battle at a time, sir.
You said he killed the John
Doe. Not Paulie Pennies?
No. His killer
is still out there.
I'll get him
tomorrow. I promise.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
MARIO: Ahem.
My father and I haven't
always seen eye to eye.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
But I think, Dad,
you'll agree that marrying Lee is
the best decision I've ever made.
- Without a doubt.
- (ALL LAUGHING)
And, Lee, you're a doctor,
a member of our city's
police department,
you're funny,
compassionate, and brilliant.
Despite insisting all dogs
are boys and all cats are girls.
It's hopeless, I've
tried to correct her.
I have loved you since
the moment I saw you.
- WOMAN: Aw!
- (ALL APPLAUD)
(CHEERING)
It's so wonderful. He's
sweet. You're so lucky.
BARBARA: Lee!
Congrats.
You look gorgeous, no surprise.
- Barbara? How did you...
- Get in?
As a plus one. With
that guy there. Hey.
Or it might have been him.
You need to leave right now.
Can't we bury the hatchet?
So I came at you with a knife,
kidnapped you, whatever.
I've forgiven you for beating me
unconscious. Water under the bridge.
You just stay right here.
I'm gonna get someone.
I'm leaving.
I just wanted to ask.
As someone else who was once
with Jim Gordon, don't you miss it?
Miss what?
The heat.
Being so close, so
much darkness and light,
to someone always
at war with himself.
Let me think.
Tormented Jim Gordon.
Or Mario, who I
know is a good man,
who'll be a wonderful
father to my children,
and whom I love.
No, I don't miss it.
Wow.
I think you actually
believe that.
(CHUCKLES) It's kind of sad.
Tell my dates I've
left, would you?
Uh-uh.
- Don't let her ruin your night.
- (SIGHS)
Captain, I'm so glad you came.
I can't stay. I came
to congratulate you.
You deserve to be happy.
Thank you.
But you have to stay
for at least one drink.
If nothing else, to save
me from these people.
One drink.
- But no work talk.
- Deal.
So, among the materials
confiscated in Symon's lab,
I came across a unique
anesthetic cocktail.
Let me guess, the same cocktail
toxicology found in the John Doe.
Exactly.
Hey. I got some bad
news. Symon walked.
What?
The girl he had tied up refused to
press charges, they probably paid her off,
and we just got an order
from Judge Bam-Bam
demanding his immediate release.
The botoxed son of a
bitch is uber-connected.
The toxicology definitely ties
Symon to the John Doe murder.
We gotta get him back here.
Captain Barnes?
Carmine Falcone. I
don't believe we've met.
No. But I was just leaving.
I see. Is my company so odious?
You belong behind bars.
I'm retired.
After running Gotham's
underworld for 30 years.
This city was built
because of men like me.
People have jobs
That whiskey you're drinking,
paid for through my work.
So you did some good. So what?
It doesn't mean
you're above the law.
Nobody is.
You know, whenever I hear a
man possessed of such certainty,
I always think he's trying
mostly to convince himself.
I wish you a pleasant
evening, Captain.
(SIGHS)
- Hey, Cap.
- Alvarez.
Tell Gordon I'm bringing him the man
responsible for Paulie Pennies' murder.
No backup. He's coming
in of his own accord.
Sure thing, Cap. But you should
know the judge released Dr. Symon.
We had to let him go.
VOICES: (WHISPERING) Guilty!
Guilty!
Guilty! Guilty!
Guilty.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Isabella?
Isabella, I got your note.
I thought you needed to
leave for your conference.
ISABELLA: I can be late, Edward.
This is more important.
Oswald... (CLEARS THROAT)
Oswald,
the Mayor, he informed
me of your position.
But believe me, I think
our breaking up is for the best.
No, Edward, it's not.
I understand your fear. It
comes from a place of love.
I know you won't hurt me.
You never could.
I don't think that you...
(GASPS)
Oh, my... (SHUDDERS)
Kristen.
I found old photos
in newspapers.
- You have to...
- I need to leave. Now!
No, no, no. Look at me!
- Look at me!
- You don't know what you're doing.
I am forcing you to face
your fear! You won't hurt me!
Even when I look
like this! Edward!
Edward.
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
No, no, no.
Edward...
(CHOKING) Edward.
Should I take the glasses off?
Keep 'em on.
Seal off the exits. But do it quietly.
Last thing anyone wants is a scene.
FEMALE OFFICER: Yes, sir.
A little late for that.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry, but we
have to make an arrest
in the Paulie Pennies case.
We tried to get the guy at home.
But his housekeeper
said he was here.
Just makes you realize what a
small town Gotham is, doesn't it?
Couldn't you wait? If he's
here, he's not exactly running.
She makes a good point,
Jim. You wanna take that one?
Good evening, everyone.
Jim, what's going on?
Apparently, there's a murder
suspect among our guests.
Can I ask who?
Dr. Maxwell Symon. He's a...
Plastic surgeon. You arrest him, you're
gonna have to fight off every woman here.
He's a favorite.
He's also a murderer.
I'd be curious to know
how your father knows him.
I'm sure that their relationship
is completely aboveboard.
While you two hash this
out. I'm gonna go grab Symon.
- Harvey.
- What?
I can handle a plastic
surgeon on my own.
Don't worry, discretion
is my middle name.
Lee, I'd like a word with Jim.
- Mario.
- It'll be fine.
Okay.
Look, Mario, I have a job
to do, so whatever this is...
When you told Tetch to kill Lee,
you knew he would do the opposite.
You sacrificed your
girlfriend for my fiancée.
- That's insane.
- Can we just admit you still love her?
- I don't have time for this.
- Hey!
You once told me that if I
ever hurt her Lee, you'd kill me.
Well, now it's my turn.
I love Lee, and I'll do
whatever I have to to keep her.
Then word of advice,
lose the jealousy.
It's weak.
Gordon.
(SPITS)
For Lee, I'll give you that one.
Oh, Captain.
If you keep frowning like that,
you'll never get those
wrinkles out around your mouth.
Come down to my office tomorrow.
I'll give you a free evaluation.
- (GRUNTING)
- (GROANING)
I'm surprised you can feel that
through that thing you call a face.
What are you doing? (GRUNTS)
What I should
have done all along.
(PANTING)
You're insane.
Oh, no, Doc.
I'm saner than I've ever been.
I'm seeing things clearly
for the very first time.
All these years, I've put
my trust in the system,
my trust in the law,
held myself back from doing
what I really wanted to do.
And then I saw the truth.
It's not just you that's guilty.
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
- (CHOKING)
This whole city is guilty.
Stop. (CONTINUES CHOKING)
You're a police
officer for God's sake.
You have to follow the law.
I don't have to do
anything. I am the law.
I am judge,
jury,
and executioner!
(SCREAMING)
(HORN BLARING)
Sentence served.
Ed.
- How'd she take it?
- What? Oh. Uh...
Everything is wonderful.
Isabella showed me that,
uh, I was worried over nothing.
I'm so happy for you.
But, why are you back?
Well, she had to go to
her conference. I insisted.
You're a good man.
But, you look done in. I will
hear all about it tomorrow.
Get some sleep.
Got to give her credit.
She fought for him.
Too bad she
underestimated her opponent.
- I'm assuming it's done.
- Yup.
Feel kind of bad though, boss.
I always liked librarians.
You?
What about poor Ed?
He will be heartbroken.
(SNIFFLES) Luckily, he
has a shoulder to cry on.
(HUMMING)
(BELL DINGING)
Uh-oh. Come on. Oh, no.
Oh, come on... Uh-oh.
Come on, come on, come on,
come... (INHALES SHARPLY)
Help me! Help me! Somebody help!
Oh, dear!
(CRASHING)
Jim, you and Mario
have a heart-to-heart?
Yeah. Where's Symon?
No luck. He must've skedaddled.
- I thought he might be at the bar.
- Uh-huh.
Look, keep a perimeter
in case he shows back up.
I'm gonna head to his house.
And, Harvey, uh,
take it easy, huh?
It's good to have
you back again, Jim.
- Uh-huh.
- I'm real glad.
Captain.
- Did you hear?
- Everything.
I saw Symon here earlier.
You managed to pick him up?
Not yet. He must've skipped out
when we showed up. We'll get him.
Alvarez said you were bringing in
the guy who did Paulie Pennies?
Turned out to be a dead end.
I'll let you know
when I find Symon.
Jim.
Things are gonna
change around here.
You and I are gonna make
a difference in this city.
We're gonna clean it up.
Yes, sir.
VOICES: Guilty!
Guilty.
- Guilty. Guilty.
- (LAUGHING)
Guilty!
Guilty.
Guilty. Guilty.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
GCPD. Sir!
(GROANING)
Dr. Symon.
Who did this?
Barnes.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English -SDH